SEBASTIAN NATALE

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

giordano_95@yahoo.com | @SebasNatale95 on LinkedIn, GitHub | Montreal, QC.

ABOUT

I'm a Full-Stack Dev, but I've based my experience in the Front-End. Jack of all trades with a couple years of experience working with the SERN stack (SQL, Express, React, Node) but I've dabbed in a bunch of other technologies like .NET and Python Back-End projects, enterprise CMSs like Sitecore and SAS-CDC, other frameworks/libraries like Angular, with some Typescript for good measure, among whatever sparks my interest.

SKILLS

- Front-End tech like HTML, CSS and JavaScript, Bootstrap and jQuery, React and Sass.
 CMSs like Wordpress, Sitecore, SAS CDC. Dabbled in TypeScript and Angular.
- Back-End tech like Node, Express, MySQL (and derivatives). Dabbled in .NET, Python/Django.
- Other "dev checklist" tech like Git, Linux, AWS experience. Arduino stuff sometimes :)
- Design and multimedia software like the Adobe suite, Logic Pro X and Cubase.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END ENGINEER

PGD LATAM, from Aug 2021 to Mar 2023

Led or worked with teams in creating multiple web solutions like web sites in Bootstrap, jQuery, full-on apps in React, Sass, or marketing campaigns and mass emails in MailChimp, for clients such as United Airlines, Wells Fargo, Zoetis, and Exact Sciences.

FULL-STACK ENGINEER

iComm Solutions, from Jun 2020 to Dec 2020

Collaborated on our telemedicine platform on mostly front-end work using React and Typescript, with some back-end tasks in Go and PostgreSQL.

EDUCATION

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Acamica, Oct 2019 to Jul 2020

BASIC PROGRAMMING COURSE

Platzi, July to Nov 2014

BACHELORS OF ARTS IN AUDIOVISUAL ART AND JAZZ PIANO

Pontificia Universidad Javeriana, 2013 to 2018. I dropped out, but still actively use the audiovisual skills in Front-End work.